No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
- My Bey.
- Ha?
The woundeds are secured by Alps.
Our Bamsı Bey's and our martyrs' bodies
are on their way to tent.
Nothing. No traces of Nicola's dogs.
No traces of Togay's soldiers.
Brother.
You'll keep looking.
You'll search until you find them.
If they are under the land...
Pluck them off!
If they are in hell...
Take them out!
If they are behind the mountains...
Go through the mountains!
They hurt my heart!
They slaughtered my father's memorial
Bamsı Bey, they slaughtered my alps!
They destroyed the head of my tent!
They are not going to die easily.
Let's go!
Brother, depart at once!
Search everywhere to Inegol Castle.
I'll go to Togay's place.
As you command, my Bey.
Let's go Alps!
Go!
Hurry up idiots!
Hurry up!
Come here Osman.
Osman will track us for taking revenge
for Bamsı Bey.
When they come, you'll fall on them.
You have to choke their souls.
Don't worry Togay.
The weakest point of a Gokboru like
Osman is his anger, Camuha.
I baited him to my trap.
He'll go mad and his
anger will lead him to death.
Hurry up!
It's time to get blood!
My Bey.
Cerkutay.
They passed here.
They're going to their place, my Bey.
My Bamsı Bey is watchin us...
We'll track them down!
We are the valiants who
follow him.
Let's go.
Leave the horses here.
Where are they my Bey?
They must have realised we were coming.
I am here Osman Bey!
Osman Bey.
Let's see what you are going to do now.
Your path ends here, Osman.
Your desire for revenge
turned you into a fool, Osman Bey!
Otherwise you wouldn't fall in this trap.
Get out of my way.
Feelings of vengeance
turned me into a lion!
Now you are between my paws!
Protect me!
For Bamsı Bey!
Attack!
Where are you Togay?
Where are you?
As that Camuha dog run away...
Togay must be somewhere else.
We're returning to tent!
We'll complete our last mission
for Bamsı Bey.
Later, we'll find those heathens!
Let's go!
Bamsı..
Crazy Bamsı has died,
is that true?
He's dead.
He roared an died.
Abdurrahman Ghazi, Savcı Bey
and finally Bamsı.
Ertugrul Ghazi's era has ended
with Bamsı.
Now it's time for his breed.
Osman will go after you, you know that.
This is what we want.
He'll disobey Geyhatu...
because of his anger...
and he'll ruin himself and
others like Umur Bey...
Disobeying Geyhatu means death.
You have to be loyal to Geyhatu, and
create an army with your soldiers.
We are going to hit Osman together.
Are you sweating, Nicola?
You were the one who killed
Yason's soldiers, Togay.
It won't be easy to take
soldiers from Governors.
I have to think about it.
If you want Geyhatu's friendship,
do not think.
Just fight.
Find soldiers.
Create an army.
Otherwise, our alliance will
turn into hostility.
I give you time until
tomorrow sunset.
I suggest you not to
make me angry.
Army aside, I won't even give you
a soldier!
What about Vali Yargucu?
I'll sound governors out.
We both now they'll reject, Nicola!
Of course Helen!
This will be our excuse!
How did Osman get out of there?
- I don't know how it happened.
- Shut up!
Gokboru...
I'll leave you to kill Nicola's soldiers!
Nicola is going to find out you
disobeyed Vali Yargucu.
I'll use him until he finds out.
"We had placed collars around their necks, right up
to their chins so that their heads are forced up
We set barriers before and behind them,
blocking their vision: they cannot see.
It is all the same to them whether...
you warn them or not:
they will not believe.
You can warn only those who will follow the
Quran and hold the Merciful One in awe,
though they cannot see Him: give such people
the glad news of forgiveness and a noble reward.
We shall certainly bring the dead back to life,
and We record what they send ahead of them
as well as what they leave behind:
We keep an account of everything in a clear record.
Give them the example of the people
to whose town messengers came.
We sent two messengers
but they rejected both.
Then We reinforced them with a third.
They said, ‘Truly,
we are messengers to you,’
but they answered, ‘You are only
men like ourselves.
The Lord of Mercy has sent nothing;
you are just lying.'
Surah Yasin [9-16]
When a ghazi dies,
when a valiant is martyred...
We need to remember them with
their battles they had.
I remember Bamsı Bey as a valiant...
whose heart beats for fighting
for Allah, for his religion.
- May Allah bless him.
- Amin.
Amin.
When I was a kid, ever time my father
Ertugrul Ghazi...
- May Allah bless him
- Amin.
goes to war, I was thinking...
if Bamsı Bey was with him or not.
His existence gave me confidince.
I'd say "good, very good...
Bamsı Bey with double sword
is with my father."
Good times old times.
Then we grew up.
He respected us because we
were sons of a Bey...
but he still educated us.
- May Allah bless him.
- Amin.
I am glad to...
have a friendship with Bamsı Bey.
He was massive like a lion.
But his heart was like a bird.
I saw him tearing up many times.
He was worried about Kayı.
He got happy for Kayı.
People thought he had
no pain inside.
However, his sorrow was great
for his martyred son.
Everybody knew his name, even our tribe.
As we heard about Ertugrul Ghazi's wars,
people would say "There is this Bamsı...
who is the man, who is the archer,
who is the warrior."
Everybody knew his name.
Then we came here, and
saw him face to face.
We figured he was even underrated.
- May he rest in heaven.
- Amin.
Ertugrul Ghazi...
Savcı Bey...
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
And now...
Bamsı Bey.
Massive valiants...
Massive valiants are under the soil.
If we don't raise new valiants
like them...
to take their place...
we'll have hard times.
We'll stand up.
We'll eternize their willing to fight.
We'll struggle for them, we'll
work for their memorial.
Inshallah (if Allah permits.)
Eyvallah (Thank you) Osman Bey.
We shall not keep you any longer,
Osman Bey.
Bismillah.
(In the name of Allah).
Not at all, my Sheik.
You honored me.
My Sheik.
Osman Bey, I shall leave too.
Umur Bey, you can wait.
Our path is same now.
Let's sit down and talk
about our upcoming moves.
Eyvallah Osman Bey,
Thank you.
Here.
I want to be a martyr too.
My Bey, why do you want it?
I'll see my prophet.
This is how things go, Cerkutay.
Some leave, some stay.
Cerkutay.
Take them Cerkutay.
Those are yours now.
FATHER!
And now my father deceased, Aygül.
You were right, Dündar Bey.
I tried to kill him many times.
We swung our blades at each other.
But the day I came to the tribe.
He took me into his tribe.
So, he trusted you.
So did...
So did I!
I took shelter in him.
I took his support.
Now I'm all alone.
You have your brothers.
You, Boran, and Göktuğ.
Aren't you three hawks?
True.
And also, you have me.
And Ahmet too!
Look.
Bamsı Bey left a son like him
behind him.
He told you that you'll be
Osman Bey's Bamsı now.
He did.
But it's not easy to be Bamsı Bey.
Why are you saying that Cerkutay?
You have a good heart like him.
You are strong like him.
You are impatient like him.
And Bamsı Bey too would make everyone
laugh back then.
Son...
So, what happened that Togay
broke the agreement?
If he had such intentions before,
he wouldn't let me alive.
What happened has happened.
We unsheathed our weapons.
They won't be sheathed before getting
wet by the blood of that heathen.
I sent news to our sultan.
He should know that we didn't break
the agreement but he did.
I wanted him to act accordingly.
In this caravan raid, not only Togay's
warriors...
but also Nikola's soldiers too were there.
-It was Nikola who sold me to Togay.
He must've done it to gain Togay's
friendship.
The grudge they hold against us
brought them together.
But we'll separate them again.
We'll break their dirty alliance...
and crush them one by one.
But firstly, Togay.
I'll take care of him first.
He was a duel-wielder.
We would draw our swords when
he said: ''Come on, children!''
It's enough that you hurt
yourself, Cerkutay.
He wasn't just your father.
Bamsı Bey was a father to us all.
He was the father of all ghazis.
We are all in pain.
Ahmet Alp.
Give me the swords.
Wait! What are you doing?
Cerkutay, it's Osman Bey's order.
These weapons are the honor and history
of the last ghazi from our old lands.
For this reason, these weapons
are very important.
They'll go to where they are belong,
Osman Bey's tent.
-Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
-Alright, alright. Wait.
Let Cerkutay spend some time
and say farewell.
But this isn't fair!
Come on, there is no time.
They are going to the tent.
What are you saying?
-Cerkutay!
-I would die before giving them!
Cerkutay, are you disobeying
Osman Bey's orders, brother?
-Come on.
-Bamsı Bey gave them to me. You know it.
He gave them to me. If Osman Bey ordered
it, alright, but...
Cerkutay! Say farewell.
This is Osman Bey's order.
Come on, brother.
Come on.
O' good Bamsı Bey!
We wanted to herald these two weapons...
to the new and real owner of them
after Bamsı Bey.
We wanted our brother to feel proud.
With the name of Allah.
My brother.
So, you played with Cerkutay? Bamsı Bey
would laugh a lot if he was here.
-You played with me, huh?
-Yes. Come.
We will avenge him...
We'll make Togay puke blood!
We swear! We swear!
We swear!
But you will pay for this joke.
With these weapons, I will avenge
Bamsı Bey first.
Then, I will avenge for
deceiving Cerkutay like this.
What will you do to them, you crazy man?
It's my responsibility to take
a worthy revenge.
What will I do to you?
With the name of Allah.
My daughter.
My dear daughter.
My Malhun.
Thank Allah that I've seen
your happiness.
And you married a valiant bey.
You came to a noble and
famous tribe.
Now, tell me.
Is everything as you wanted?
I knew that I was coming to a
tribe with a Khatun.
So, I didn't expect everything to be
as I wanted.
Look, daughter...
there are two kinds
of people in this world.
Good and bad people.
The hostility, hatred, and anger
of the bad never ends.
Because the source is the
darkness in their hearts.
But there are no hatred or grudge
in the hearts of the good.
Their hostility is temporal.
After all, their hearts
are clean.
Clean hearts can't keep hostility
for long.
My pretty daughter.
I vouch for you. I know that
your heart is clean.
And about Bala Hatun.
Even a wood can't leave devious
from Edebali's lodge.
But we were devious.
We left the word we gave him.
And we paid the price.
Not at all, father.
It is, it is. We were blind.
Edebali is the light of the Turks.
We were without the light and blinded.
So, what I'm saying is...
be patient. Be patient.
You raised me, father.
And you still do.
May Allah protect you.
May I enter?
Come.
-I've talked to Zoe. She'll come tomorrow.
-Bring her to me directly.
Osman, I know...
I know...
You will avenge me.
But, firstly...
Firstly...
Think for my children.
May I enter, my bey?
Come.
Thank Allah, Osman. He lives as
he wanted and died as he lived.
-We witnessed it.
-We have, Bala.
We witnessed it.
And we'll avenge him.
Soon, inshlalah.
Soon.
May Allah keep your sword sharp, Osman.
May Allah give you strenght.
Bala, you are supporting me.
You stand beside me.
Until death knocks on my door, Osman.
You are the pole of my tent.
Alps! If the enemy thinks twice,
you'll think treble.
You will think of the places that even
the devil can't!
Arms, armpit, belt...
legs, boots, every place!
Caps!
Back! Every place!
Do you understand? Come on!
Just like that.
Zoe?
Tell me, why are you here?
First, you invited me to the tribe.
Now, Malhun Hatun did.
Malhun Hatun? Why?
I'll find out if you allow me.
Alps!
Come on alps, go on!
My bey, he wants to speak.
-Tell me.
-Firstly, my condolences, Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you.
Tell me.
I've changed my mind.
If you still want it, I want to
sell me property.
What made you change your decision?
I thought that this would be the best.
Our wound is still fresh.
Let us talk this later.
-Then allow me.
-Of course.
-Boran.
-Yes, my bey.
We'll talk about this later.
-As you order, my bey.
-Go.
-My bey.
-Tell me.
It's from Konya Palace, my bey.
Call my brother and Davud Bey
to my tent.
I'll talk to Osman Bey. If it's good
with you, I want you to be with us.
You'll be a company for Yaren
and see us as your family.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
I was at a fruit garden for years.
I've never had a family.
No one treated me like you did before.
I don't know what to say.
You don't need to say a thing. They'll
prepare a tent for you. Your new home.
May it be good, then, Zoe.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
You won't regret it.
You held the hand of a lonely woman.
You made her happy.
May Allah bless you. But, you are
Malhun Hatun.
You never act without a plan.
Tell me, what's on your mind?
I've done what I should, Alaca.
We shouldn't be alone.
She knows the area, especially
Söğüt. She'll accompany us well.
Zoe!
What did you talk about with Malhun Hatun?
-Why are you curious?
Wouldn't I be curious?
And I...
-What about you?
-I'm curious, don't you get it?
And I say why.
I think about you.
Don't you understand?
Do you think about everyone who
visits the tribe?
I think about you.
Zoe!
Won't you say a thing?
Malhun Hatun took me under
her service.
Malhun Hatun? How so?
Alaca. She praised me a lot.
She said that I can do anything.
She can watch over the chickens
and ducks here.
She'll have a place to call home and
have a good life, she told her.
-So?
-So, I'm a tribeswoman now.
I'll live in Kayı Tribe now.
-Why are you smiling?
-I haven't heard such good news lately.
-So, you are happy?
-Happy? I want to fly!
Come, let's get your things.
Then, I'll show you around.
Sultan Mesut says that Togay rebelled
against the Mongol governor.
Now, Togay is a rebel.
And we aren't facing the Ilkhaganete!
When we go after him, no one will
stand behind him.
And if we break his alliance
with Nikola...
Sooner or later...
with or without Nikola,
he'll die by my hands.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in!
-My bey, the lord of Bilecik is here.
-Take him in.
Come.
-My condolences, Osman Bey.
-Thank you. Thank you.
I want to express my sincere empathy
for Bamsı Bey's deah.
Thank you.
-I have important news, Osman Bey.
-Tell me.
Lately, Mongols visit İnegöl Castle
frequently.
Not only you, my friend, but also
the emperor won't like this.
I have an ear in the castle.
As I heard, Togay wanted Nikola
to gather men to attack you.
He'll go to the lords.
Even though it will be difficult, they'll
build a big army.
You must know what they want
to do with it.
We know what they'll want to do.
The important thing is what we will do.
Thank Allah we did as Bamsı Bey
wanted.
With the money he left, many poor
people filled their stomachs.
-Thank Allah. May Allah protect our tribe.
-Amin.
-Good day, ladies.
-Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
-Who is our guest?
-Her name is Zoe. She'll be my helper.
There were many women to help
Osman Bey's wife in the tribe.
What does that indicate, Bala Hatun.
I want to know.
If my word meant something,
I would ask earlier, Malhun Hatun.
She is honest. She is capable.
She is diligent and she has
no family.
-And I opened my arms.
-Mashallah. Good thinking.
Bala Hatun!
I show you respect and
I expect respect.
I remind you that no one is in a position
to question or order the other.
I didn't question nor order.
I just reminded.
If you'll do as you want, don't let
me stop you.
I've heard it by an accident.
Did Malhun Hatun do something
to bother you?
New people come to the tribe every day.
Isn't it my right to know who they are?
It's been days only...
and she is forming her own order.
Both Bala and Malhun Hatun doesn't
seem to step back.
It's up to you, to their friends,
to hold them back.
Osman Bey has a lot to do.
He shouldn't hear this.
The time I've given you is over, Nikola
Will you fight like a soldier?
Or will you let me bury you under
this stone tent with my warriors...
by staying here like a woman?
-My army is ready!
You can't do this, sir.
Yaso...
will bring 200 more soldiers from
the other lords...
and we'll strike the last blow
on Osman together.
You look very fiery to spill blood,
Nikola...
you are growling here like a jackal
that smelled blood...
but you too know that blood makes a jackal
crazy but it's not enough to beat its fear!
I wanted to spill the blood of the Turks
for years, Togay!
-Now, you roar like a tiger!
-I'm neither a jackal nor a tiger!
I'm a soldier, Togay! A good soldier
who knows the price of losing you.
The door!
Why? Why did you do this, sir?
Live the moment.
Don't trust tomorrow at all.
I'm a soldier!
-Welcome, my bey.
-Thank you. Thank you.
In many battles, you stood by me
with this sword.
I'm concerned that I won't
be with you anymore.
You are a Khatun of this
tribe now.
You can't put yourself at risk.
I want to be with my alps and
take revenge from Togay.
Tomorrow, we'll take revenge on them...
at Kızılbey Ormanı, for every soldier
and woman of the tribe.
-Tomorrow?
-Tomorrow indeed. They'll attack then.
-Osman Bey, I--
-Malhun Hatun.
Tell me. Have you get used
to the tribe?
-I will get used to it.
-What about...
choosing women to help you?
-Alaca will be with me.
And this Rum girl who lives in Söğüt,
Zoe.
I talked to her. She'll be our helper,
if you allow it.
Come here.
Come, Malhun Hatun.
-Tell me.
-Tell you what?
What's your dream?
What do you want in this
temporal world?
What would you enjoy talking about?
Tell me.
If you want to listen, let me tell you,
Osman Bey.
It's the time we were waiting for, Nikola.
An army seeking Turkish blood awaits.
No one can save Kayıs from us now.
Turks say ''The arrow has already left
the bow''.
We'll see who'll get shot.
I told you I was going to make
Nicola my soldier.
Nicola obeys me now.
In the way of Genghis Khan...
With the wrath of my father Noyan...
Swords will spit blood..
For Erlik Khan...
- Death!
- Death! Death! Death!
I am here for my father Noyan!
Father, I am here for you!
I am here to shed Turkish blood!
To defeat Togay, we have to draw them
in a narrow valley, Aykurt.
They are not used to fight somewhere
else than a moorland.
We'll fight in a field, Turanalp.
Do not join if you don't want to.
I have made my decision, Goktug.
Alaca, you are a Kayı Hatun.
Do not forget that.
- You have to always listen to me.
- Don't worry, Aygül Hatun.
Osman Bey, as you commanded, Umur Bey
will join us in Karacabey plateau.
Eyvallah(okay) brother.
Eyvallah.
Bamsı Bey is not with us but
his swords are, aren't they?
- Aren't they, Cerkutay?
- His son Cerkutay...
is going to take revenge, my Bey.
This is the day.
My Alps!
We were raised by the stories
Bamsı Bey told us.
However, they were not just stories...
They shall show the way to
our valiants, our sons.
We are enhanced by the honor of
Bamsı Bey and Abdurrahman Ghazi.
If we do not take revenge for them...
Then the stories they told us shall
be haram to us!
Let them be!
Then the horses we ride to war
shall not carry us!
They shall not!
This way ends in vengeance.
If we return, this world shall be
a dungeon to us!
It shall be!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest.
This is the most difficult part of
being a Bey's Hatun.
To wait.
I am not used to this.
I was always with my father.
I was there in wars.
This is how it's like to be
a tent Hatun.
You just wait.
You know what to do.
Do not disobey me.
This is your game, Togay.
My soldiers will cover all the ways out.
We won't let any Turk run away.
Yason, lead your soldiers.
Osman's head is mine.
No, Togay. Whoever wants more
will take it.
Osman is coming
They are waiting for us, my Bey.
That's fine, our prey came to us.
Soldier!
Get ready!
Soldiers! Get ready!
Soldiers, get ready!
Come to me.
Why don't we attack, Osman Bey?
Umur Bey, be patient.
Be patient.
Come to me.
Attack!
Geyhatu's hunter dog
Black Shaman Togay!
We are even now!
We are even!
Just now.
Seljuq Sultan says Togay is a rebel.
Helping Togay meant recieving
Ilkhanate's support.
But now, it means opposing Ilkhanate.
Ilkhanate state on one side, Kayi tribe
on the other side.
Nicola.
Are you that strong?
Or is Togay, who escapes from his
own state, strong enough?
Only one reason is not enough, Gündüz Bey.
You need more...
If you want me to betray.
Isn't it enough that we let you keep...
your head on your body?
Alps!
For Bamsı Bey!
For Abdurrahman Ghazi!
For all of our martyrs!
Attack!
In the name of Erlik Han...
Slaughter them!
Wait alps!
Wait.
Cowards!
Togay, Togay, Togay.
You knocked the door of
the angel of death...
by disobeying the heir of Geyhatu..
by disobeying me, disobeying Yargucu!
Osman Bey!
Vali Yargucu!
This dog who violated the agreement and
killed my alps...
is mine!
Osman Bey!
I'll take Togay to Sivas!
I'll show everyone how the disobeyers
end up.
Do not insist!
Otherwisei you'll pay dearly.
Bring them!
Osman Bey, what are we going to do?
Are we done with this ignoble dog here?
Don't worry brother.
It is not over...
until Osman Bey says so.
Alps!
Alps! Clear the way!
Hurry!
Take them!
I'll kill you in a
meeting of Noyans in Sivas.
Everybody will see that disobeying
Geyhatu means disobeying me.
Why did you obey this betrayer?
You diverged from Genghis Khan's rules,
Yargucu! You sold your soul for gold!
My soul is not for sale!
Crush him!
Stop!
Death is his salvation!
He'll walk to Sivas.
I'll crush him in each step of mine!
He'll pay for treason in each step!
We're leaving!
My Bey, they took the way
near the Gorklu Mountain.
There are too many places to set
an ambush.
They were too many, Osman Bey.
If we fight, we'll have so much martyrs.
We'll handle, but not by fighting.
We are going to have many opportunities
until they arrive in Sivas.
You took revenge for my soldiers.
ı appreciate you, High Nicola.
I am raising my glass for you.
To our victory and you.
To our victory and you!
Togay ended himself by
betraying his master.
Nicola, the victory you won by
not facing Geyhatu...
impowered us.
What about Osman?
Not only us, Yason...
Osman Bey gained strenght too.
Umur Bey and other Beys joined him.
As I heard, he has
Seljuqi Sultan's support.
Seljuqi Sultan needs to
cover himself first!
If Sultan wants to face Byzantine Emperor
to protect Osman, I won't stop him.
- To victory!
So you used Nicola, huh?
If we could have killed Togay,
we'd have a great victory.
However, as Togay is still alive...
he continues to be a threat for us,
Osman Bey.
How did you convince Nicola, my Bey?
When Vali learned Togay
disobeyed him...
Sultan Mesud sent me a secret messenger.
Politics paved the way for victory.
Sultan showed that he valued
Osman Bey.
So you used Nicola with this information.
Vali may have ruined Osman Bey's plan...
but we don't have a trouble like
Togay anymore.
He can't escape from Vali Yargucu.
My Bey, we know you won't stop.
What is your plan?
Bamsı Bey was my father's memorial.
I considered him a father.
If I don't take revenge...
The sky and the ground will
cast me out!
I would upset my Beys!
Brother, how can I sleep when
I go to bed?
I have...
a promise for Bamsı Bey.
I am going to take revenge for him and
martyr Alps from Togay!
I swear that Togay's death is going to be...
committed by me!
Inshallah (if Allah permits).
Osman Bey.
How are we going to take that dog
from Vail's hands?
If we face Ilkhanate, all the
relationship you've been working on...
will be ruined.
This would surpass us.
You are right, Umur Bey.
You are right.
But I am not going to oppose Ilkhanate,
I'm going to oppose just Togay to kill him.
I'll catch him while he runs away
from Vali.
Brother!
Get the alps ready.
We're going to do one last mission
for Bamsı Bey.
Osman Bey, Vali will pass through
Germiyan land to arrive Sivas.
He's going to spend the night there.
I witnessed so many times that they
used that way.
They are good with Germiyan Bey.
Germiyan Land, huh?
This information is handy.
Who knows Germiyan land the best is...
Turanalp.
- Boran!
- My Bey.
Summon Turanalp immediately!
Yes my Bey.
Can I come in?
Come.
They're searching for Togay everywhere.
They'll find Geyhatu's dog eventually.
I know.
A new bride shouldn't have
such mournful eyes, Malhun Hatun?
The new bride is going to pale in this
tent like a wildflower, Alaca.
You are not only a beautiful wildflower,
you are now a Hatun of Kayı tribe.
Don't talk like that.
I climed over the mountains with my sword,
fighting like a man.
I am glad to have a fellow like you.
I'll be your friend until the end,
Malhun Hatun.
But, Osman Bey is the man
of your heart.
He is the man of your tent.
Look where you are.
Look around.
You are in the tent of a man
who you fell in love with.
I reached the happy end, is that right?
Yes, thank Lord we've come this far.
I am so happy for you.
Do you think I don't realise
your love for Osman Bey in your eyes?
Do you think I don't know
how much your heart wants him?
Do you think Osman Bey doesn't know it?
He knows, isn't he?
Of course.
If he knows, how are our hearts
going to meet...
while our even our eyes can't meet?
Tell me Alaca.
Bamsı Bey was like his father.
He just lost his father.
And now, it's Bamsı Bey.
Isn't this what describes love,
Mahlun Hatun? To yearn for beloved one...
and the sorrow of this.
He doesn't share his sorrow, his pain,
even his happiness with me.
How can he share his love with me?
Our eyes can't even meet in
uncharted nights.
My love can't reach him.
Malhun.
You should leave.
I have work to do.
Oh Osman Bey.
I wish you let me be with you.
I wish you looked me in the eye.
I wish you let me put my head
over your knee.
Welcome sir. Welcome.
You brought us honor.
I sent away everyone as I heard
you were coming.
No one is here except for you.
Sir, I made spare rib for you.
I know you love it.
Hurry up.
I had a long way.
My soldiers on guard outside
are also hungry!
Set Vali Hadrat's table at once!
Carry food to thesoldiers!
Take them to basement.
Don't worry sir.
There is a cell that even a mouse
can't enter.
Take them, take them!
Son.
Show the way to soldiers.
Tell me.
There are tens of soldiers, my Bey.
We can't get near.
Keep your eyes wide open until Turanalp
brings Togay.
How can my Bey trust him so much, Boran?
He is a newbie.
What are we going to do Togay?
You sharpen your teeth if you don't
have a sword.
Let your wrath keep you strong.
I brought food.
Clumsy idiot!
I got it.
Hurry up!
What is this mess?
Did you drop the food?
You clumsy!
I can get you out of here
in return of a good deal of gold.
How?
Gold is a key to all the doors, Togay.
I'll wait for you.
Togay!
Leave the man!
Get out of there.
Can we trust this man, Togay?
We won't trust him.
We'll trust the power of gold.
If we go to Sivas...
we're done.
Stop there.
Follow me.
Come on!
There are too many soldiers outside.
Where are we going to go?
I know a secret passage.
Let's go.
Togay, Togay.
Turan will bring that dog safe
and sound, inshallah (if Allah permits).
Inshallah.
This is not a mission
for a new guy in the tribe.
He is the guy, I think.
Either he brings Togay, or
I know what to do.
He'll get Togay among all those
animals...
and convince him, then bring
him here.
Turanalp's mission is extremely difficult,
Osman Bey.
A valiant shines in such missions,
brother.
He'll overcome for sure.
Inshallah (If Allah permits)
Come on, hurry up!
Why did we stop?
Togay!
Osman.
Pagan Noyan's son...
Pagan Togay.
Now wish luck from your Gods.
I have been fighting for my father
for a long time.
Let my teeth taste blood, Osman Bey.
So you want to fight me, huh?
Toe to toe.
Alps!
For your holy soul, father!
Gokboru, souls shall...
take your life!
From now on, our Lord shall help you.
Go now.
A wolf herd continues as a wolf herd.
Your teeth can't bite Gokboru.
Everyone will take a lesson
from your death.
Now...
it's time to take revenge!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com